{"id": "3XDSWAMB246TTF2NW6ALKCP4V9GCQG##3K9FOBBF2KY4G6HVJTH58LGB9EQNLV##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_1385180##q1_a1##3AXFSPQOYSCJA4IKSIGDVHYLGIGFJN", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Until we can get you an ice pack that 'll have to do . \" She held it in her hands like a treasure , sparkling . \" Thank you so much Fujimoto - san ! \" Before he could fight back another blush she had opened the can and was chugging it back . His jaw dropped and he was momentarily flabbergasted . The crowd murmured in concern and disapproval .\n\nQuestion: What may the female subject have drank based off reactions ?", "options": {"A": "She may have drank water .", "B": "She may have drank alcohol .", "C": "She may have drank some tap water .", "D": "She may have drank juice ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 20952, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3XQ4XW3ODBQS8DPYRHAK3ZVJ3V42SI##3ZSY5X72N0QX1PCKPSEE9MPF9SLORU##A3PPLDHC3CG0YN##Blog_985759##q1_a1##3ZUE82NE0CFUQNM11EJM6RP70HDF8E", "type": "mcq", "stem": "He placed his hand on David 's head , running his hand throwing his hair in a very comforting manner . \" I ' m going to be right here , okay ? \" Michael told David . He felt the musician nod .\n\nQuestion: What may the musician be getting ready for ?", "options": {"A": "An interview .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "A tour .", "D": "A concert ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 3648, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3WUVMVA7ODHEES6GZOX75ABK2CRZAE##36U2A8VAG4EN8Z3R5VEFA113U4BYKX##A29RROPO0Z90XV##Blog_1183346##q1_a1##3JYPJ2TAYKMFWFLINVLXSDKYQ8BPF7", "type": "mcq", "stem": "First the bad news : Even though the movie 's called Booty Call , you wo n't be seeing Vivica A. Fox 's booty in the hook - up comedy . Now the good news : Viv 's shivs do make a pointed appearance . In the free pic of Vivica A.\n\nQuestion: Why does he want to see her booty ?", "options": {"A": "He does n't like Vivica .", "B": "He is attracted to Vivica .", "C": "He wanted to see a fox .", "D": "He is attracted to men ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 819, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3UV0D2KX1OXT7MZZPBT9PF92YZ4F42##3OVR4I9USSYTLVN2TTA5QY95YA64QE##A2WPPQC8S3ICVZ##Blog_836283##q1_a1##3ZRKL6Z1EAHIN7X5QWV953PLE7UGSP", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Ok , So i had went camping for almost two weeks , and it was a blast ! Me and my cousin had went swimming , and we had met these boys up at the beach . And one was so flipping HOT his name is Chad .\n\nQuestion: What may be true about me ?", "options": {"A": "I am afraid of the ocean .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "I have a boyfriend .", "D": "I like spending time outdoors ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 24299, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3YD0MU1NC2ZG0T13WVTOMSUDYZ47A3##36U2A8VAG2X8DA4KLY2FI3DUHUNKYD##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_772473##q1_a1##3A9LA2FRWSCPPVF8KE7EXDU5E1KHXN", "type": "mcq", "stem": "God answered my prayers ! I knew that we would be working on our anniversary but I sent out a prayer that please , please could He make it a special one for me ? I am such a sucker for celebrating events .\n\nQuestion: Why did the narrator pray to god to avoid work ?", "options": {"A": "The narrator loved work over celebrating personal events .", "B": "The narrator had no desire to celebrate their anniversary .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "The narrator truly loved their work and was passionate about it ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 9012, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3D06DR5225HZLW8Q01VD5AR3TOZAMH##30H4UDGLT3G9UKCMFNJCKPCM2QMMPP##A13H5EYMWJ9GU8##Blog_523693##q1_a1##3L1EFR8WWT3FA364M8D0EPWARI3F9P", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I got a laundry last night , and I dare say I am as excited as a woman who has just upgraded from a wringer to a brand true electric washing machine . Or from a washboard to a wringer . Or from a stone in the river to a washboard ... well you get the idea .\n\nQuestion: Why was the woman excited", "options": {"A": "She just repaired her washing machine", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "She just got a new washing machine", "D": "She just bought some new clothes"}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 8024, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "33P2GD6NRNQJ5VG1LVSP7JM3I9HHK8##39ZSFO5CA9UWLHEXTC5EE374AS0JUT##AS5X6GRDJKWG3##Blog_462526##q1_a1##3VADEH0UHEBO0KQ4TFLWZC3CE6CPSA", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I look over my shoulder and the man is sweating like two rats in a wool sock ; very Flashdance - esque . Finally he and his stench leave . I look over at the treadmill . It 's covered in sweat .\n\nQuestion: What might be a fact about the person in this situation ?", "options": {"A": "They are trying to lose weight by working out .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "They are working out at a gym .", "D": "They are trying to build muscle at the gym ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 7314, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "31MCUE39BKKZ91DJGJI85XT0SX43GQ##3H8DHMCCWA95FZ9TP2F15I3T4PIKDD##A1DBE2OL84TBKB##Blog_1273764##q1_a1##3WGZLY9VCJ0XS385A8OWIRMMO0E8D5", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Tocadisco is playing there next Friday and it 's only 5 bucks to get in so I 'll definitely be back there next week . I ' m really in love with this city . Walking around tonight was fun and I feel like I ' m getting more of a grip on where things are . I ' m amazed by how lenient the herb laws are here in San Fran .\n\nQuestion: Why Does he love San Francisco so much ?", "options": {"A": "It is a lot warmer than the old city", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "A lot of his hobbies are cheap or free", "D": "He is free to grow herbs"}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 4572, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3Z8UJEJOC1RZOGPIMBOY5EVLGWD938##3QXNC7EIPLA6U8OFTQCHS0T33LA092##A3218IMDX9KLPJ##Blog_794674##q1_a2##3Z8UJEJOC1RZOGPIMBOY5EVLHU739T", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Seeing as I was in bed at just past 6 AM or so and had to get up at 12 to get ready , it was quite understandable why I was n't entirely too proud with myself as I went to bed . Strangely , though , I managed to get up on time and even showered and all that jazz . I was n't entirely able to stomach any breakfast , though , so I ended up having a few Pepsis which was probably not the best idea in the world . As I headed off towards Tina 's , I found myself staggering a bit too much for my liking , so I ended up having to really pull myself together to appear somewhat normal and coherent as I arrived .\n\nQuestion: What may be a plausible reason I was staggering on the way to Tina â€™s ?", "options": {"A": "I only got a few hours of sleep .", "B": "I drank too much pepsi .", "C": "I could not stomach my breakfast .", "D": "I was walking as if I felt way too proud of myeslf ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 24132, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3P888QFVX3SF8F0J2D7CNEVDTFFQOH##32UTUBMZ7HUQGD5LAA22C1QAIMCVB7##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_1407163##q1_a2##3G3AJKPCXN6Z7DGUU1LXE0GI43W4YC", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Serious diet pills are intended for people who are overweight to the point of being considered obese . Therefore , they are known as anti - obesity drugs ; and should not be used for quick , temporary weight loss . Diet medications and supplements will not simply \" melt \" away all your unwanted fat and permanently solve any weight problem you might have . Most weight loss trials show that diet pills offer ( at best ) short term support . You should use diet pills in combination with a simple plan for weight loss through regular exercise and an improved diet .\n\nQuestion: Why is the narrator so down on diet pills ?", "options": {"A": "They do n't believe they should be legal .", "B": "They do n't believe anything can make them lose weight .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "They do n't believe they do what they claim ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 3358, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3T6SSHJUZHO7PK04B81YMDWDG3DIIC##32N49TQG3JX0SSZ0OTE69OUDY2VAVA##AO33H4GL9KZX9##Blog_1305958##q1_a1##3P458N04Q3V04UBXLRG727CBI8R2X7", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I got a little scared , ngl . I ' m home alone and it kept thundering and lightening and pouring . And now I ' m laying on my couch with Lady Bug and Charlie . And Bogie is laying on the floor next to us :] I feel like I ' m going to throw up .\n\nQuestion: Why is everyone sitting nearby each other during the thunderstorm ?", "options": {"A": "Because being near each other makes us feel the thunderstorm is bigger .", "B": "Because being near each other makes us feel safer and more comfortable .", "C": "Because being near each other makes us feel more dangerous and daring .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 22174, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3D17ECOUOG9HZBMNIY95Q8D2J9R31A##3ND9UOO81NHU30Q9BU8S44T262EWL7##A3PPLDHC3CG0YN##Blog_1266623##q1_a1##3U18MJKL1W08QIPVGEI4GIUZSZKNCZ", "type": "mcq", "stem": "So finally I have the time to make some more updates . School has started and I ' m on a bus for one hour going and one hour coming back . That s the price you pay to go to the best all girls school in the district .\n\nQuestion: Why do n't they have much spare time ?", "options": {"A": "School is taking up their time .", "B": "Family is taking up their time .", "C": "Extracurricular activities are taking up their time .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 24270, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3VCK0Q0PO5C921V8K0DKTJ4QQZ10NZ##3JNQLM5FT5KTWVTVDD7LOZP4WCGL2I##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_1073242##q1_a2##3O2Y2UIUCS8ELOO2A3GPWWYYVE5KFU", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I had heard they were out of the meatball and I got anxious my order was n't going to be filled , so when I found out that mine was the last meatball sandwich , I was so excited I nearly peed . But it was n't that good . Neon pink , so I thought that meant it would be bursting with flavor , like Bubblicious or something , but no ! alas !\n\nQuestion: Why did the narrator have a great lunch ?", "options": {"A": "They got the first meatball sandwich .", "B": "They got a fine date to join them .", "C": "They got exactly what they ordered .", "D": "They got vegetarian meatballs ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 17870, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3PZDSVZ3J5FQ1PD9310M5MU37104NI##3ZR9AIQJUC7Q2DJWSY4QJUUECHS04O##A37IJGXG1VEBEK##Blog_463879##q1_a1##3IZVJEBJ6CYDRQUD9BGVP59Y6F3Z6Y", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Speed II 9/10 Monsoonz 10/10 Both kites produce colossal amounts of lift . Stand on the beach and pull down the bar ... up you go . The Monsoonz was my favourite here for sure ... pull in the bar and up I went ... ooohhh baby ! ! ... it was love at first flight ... I guess this why they go up wind so well .\n\nQuestion: What kind of product was I reviewing ?", "options": {"A": "A hang glider", "B": "A surfboard", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "A airplanr"}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 2848, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3421H3BM9CVA9UR7PWGLLLCADPH9JV##3R08VXYT7FAVOF17707ILZB1CE87W1##A3PPLDHC3CG0YN##Blog_696570##q1_a1##3EFNPKWBMU2HSM15MF55C3USEVW037", "type": "mcq", "stem": "He could hear her breathing - slow , regulated . He felt that familiar pang from somewhere inside the darkness that he denied . That slow , relaxed - unknowing - breathing of prey being watched . He selfishly would miss these moments if she was turned .\n\nQuestion: What may be the reason for someone being so jealous of breathing ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "They have a respiratory illness .", "C": "They are n't human .", "D": "They are an animal ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 19349, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "388FBO7JZRR6ZWRTS8OTLBYA2LXYNX##3LKC68YZ3B1NEWUZ4PCK4N9NWS7OWK##AS5X6GRDJKWG3##Blog_1144267##q2_a1##3VLL1PIENS23GW0H972P65VPRQVZO7", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I think I need to go to the bridge tonight . I need to calm my heart and mind . I was told that it appears that no man will ever settle me . This statement is false because one man once did and did it successfully for over 6 years .\n\nQuestion: What may be a fact about this person ?", "options": {"A": "No one wants to settle down with them .", "B": "They will be single for a long time .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "They had a failed long - term relationship ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 13825, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3909MD9T21VBZOWSEH5MY1LTBOZEF8##3DHE4R9OCZQS5SE1MJM535858AIG2I##A3PPLDHC3CG0YN##Blog_988620##q1_a1##3B9XR6P1WG9TXN64NGUHCR712BPJBV", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Cos of her really frizzy hair and low voice ... It was so freaking cold so I ' m really impressed by these actors ' professionalism , they were prancing about ( at least Desdemona was ) in thin clothing and they still acted so well . I was like shivering in my seat throughout , especially during the first half when I did n't have my jacket . Ran up to my room during the 15 min interval for my jacket and spoke to Cassio and Othello with Ernest and Sid . But I was still damn cold and kept on fidgeting during the play .\n\nQuestion: What may be the reason for them not bringing the jacket with them in the first place ?", "options": {"A": "They did n't think they would need it .", "B": "They are usually always hot .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "They did n't think they would be staying for the whole show ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 1041, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "36818Z1KV5RDTZZNEH2Y1965N5IA3U##3OONKJ5DKFYALIVVTVSO97KBRAQOBX##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_299306##q1_a1##38RHULDV90TPQFK90P5DN45LYGCIWR", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Will they be quick to criticize when promised jobs do not materialize , the national debt does not decline , and jobs continue to go overseas ? Will they , whose candidate is elected President think all of their problems will vanish , and never to reappear ? Nothing is further from the truth . History shows that power remains in the hands of a chosen few , no matter who is President .\n\nQuestion: What is the narrator so focused on and ranting about ?", "options": {"A": "They are ranting about power supply .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "They are ranting about politics .", "D": "They are ranting about the President of Canada ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 976, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "35O6H0UNLUUR87PVM6349578R0DJ57##3DIP6YHAPF757TKZW55IDT0WHT18E0##A1GV0UZU0T2ORS##Blog_280385##q2_a2##3P458N04Q3V04UBXLRG727CCJ3FX2J", "type": "mcq", "stem": "At this point i really need to stress how much of a religious experience i had with the Osama Tezuka exhibition that was going on on the first floor of of the place . For those of you not too familiar with anime or manga culture , Tezuka was the main originator of ALL the genres of anime that are being pooped out today . And compared to the crazy epic manga he produced in the 1960s and 70s , today 's manga is all pretty much recycled crap .\n\nQuestion: What can we deduce about the narrator in this passage ?", "options": {"A": "They do n't like Osama Tezuka .", "B": "They are a manga fan .", "C": "They are religious .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 3070, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3BDORL6HKMRT5GHN9LZLP2Z9TMJRCH##3GGAI1SQEYD5VK2PUF96SN1OEZWMCG##A3PPLDHC3CG0YN##Blog_1434547##q1_a1##3AA88CN98RHKLF5XFT8DLH5E1S1KY3", "type": "mcq", "stem": "We ' ve barely finished painting the rooms . I ' ve hired someone to change the floor in the basement from ( ugh ) carpet to wood ( laminate ) . I ca n't afford real hardwood now , and the quality of today 's laminates are good enough .\n\nQuestion: What may be the reason for someone hiring someone to install the flooring ?", "options": {"A": "They do n't want the flooring installed .", "B": "They are helping someone out by paying them to do it .", "C": "They do n't know how to do it .", "D": "They do n't like flooring ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 7164, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3XQ4XW3ODBQS8DPYRHAK3ZVJ3TGS2G##3TS1AR6UQTTTDTFCHBXIHBP1G3HF7T##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_1360236##q1_a1##3P7RGTLO6GRJPX7UZNUXIVN7Y1PAKA", "type": "mcq", "stem": "The music was amazing and the food was possibly the best I ' ve ever had . Half the Island was a wildlife preserve so there were beautiful birds everywhere . I ca n't even give a good description of what it all looked and smelled like , I would not do it justice .\n\nQuestion: Why was there so much wildlife around ?", "options": {"A": "It was at a zoo .", "B": "It was protected lands .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "It was at a zoo - like amusement park ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 7623, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3ZQX1VYFTFJOW0ZU0H2CTLYLQHDO8E##3PH3VY7DJOCE8P7DQVZ1CJ40HZ1ZWG##AABCSDU3TZLNG##Blog_668164##q2_a1##35U0MRQMULLM7CV78ADMLZIT36DOV2", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I had the scariest experience ever last night , and I was in a car this time!My brother - in - Law and I were coming home from his birthday dinner and as he was turning left onto a street , my husband said \" bike \" , which did n't register to anyone else at firat until he yelled \" BIKE ! ! \" and we saw a woman whiz past in my BIL 's headlights , a mere couple of feet from his bumper . He slammed on the breaks and we were all like \" HOLY SHIIIIIT ! ! ! \"\n\nQuestion: How did we feel after the brother - in - law stopped ?", "options": {"A": "We were full from eating .", "B": "We were stunned and shocked .", "C": "We wanted to ride bikes .", "D": "We were slammed and broken ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 16559, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3KTZHH2ONIDL28FB33BZ9JL83008MC##3VE8AYVF8NVIIILO7JDO3DXNHTJF8T##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_453107##q1_a2##3FO95NVK5CYUI87CM9DLC9FJMX4SRF", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Mentally ill mothers who were unable to understand how to meet their children 's needs raised many of my Schizophrenic and depressed clients . Over our years together , when a depressive fog floated from the wings , Jim tried his best to understand my experience . One of the ways he helped was by carrying on as usual .\n\nQuestion: What may the narrator think if he has a new mentally disturbed patient ?", "options": {"A": "That they had a bad stretch in life lately .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "That they had a ill parent growing up .", "D": "That they are in need of medicine ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 19726, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "336OE47KI4YUCL49ZW4W2TVF6MRWVT##3Z4AIRP3C9SW2TRVSPMVM8YVJUP1X3##A2CMYWI1J292YJ##Blog_13505##q1_a2##3VGET1QSZ2DS1V3DHY1GWFFDLH87WT", "type": "mcq", "stem": "We called every kennel in the metropolitan area to find that they were a ) booked solid or b ) charged quadruple our regular rate . No way were we taking our carsick - prone pooch with us . Thank goodness for our fabulous friends T. & T. who agreed to dog sit . We owe them a lifetime supply of adult beverages . Then , our neighbor stole our car .\n\nQuestion: Why are they charging much more than before ?", "options": {"A": "They are trying to recoup the renovation cost .", "B": "They are featured in a pet magazine .", "C": "Supply is much smaller than demand now .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 869, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3QREJ3J433VLRRZRCG7NZBFAZ4IKL2##308XBLVESJ2YN6O41QXSB417XNOBRX##A32W24TWSWXW##Blog_820789##q1_a1##36D1BWBEHPFPAICT7KEYRQWDBFLM27", "type": "mcq", "stem": "After that discussion we said a few thanks for the Light and she asked what I 'd learned about holy power . As a student of axe and spell , I told her of what I knew , which was n't much beyond simple spells and prayers , but I think she was pleased , and we ate well that night . Next morning , Pa was really thinking we needed to explore . There was some place he was trying to find , some memory from the wars that happened there . Unfortunately the Murlocs had taken over but we did n't know that then . It was a little shack in the middle of the swampy northern Wetlands , there was no one around when we came upon it .\n\nQuestion: What may have been the reason we were in danger when we went to the shack ?", "options": {"A": "The area had been taken over by an enemy and we were trespassing on their turf .", "B": "We had no food at the time and were weak because we had n't eaten for several days .", "C": "I had learned too much about the holy power and that was detrimental when dealing with Murlocs .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 18390, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3HJ1EVZS2OHQYRMXWUCK4177UYT3RK##3IXQG4FA2UWSJ6SI79X6KJ1DPCIB9U##A37IJGXG1VEBEK##Blog_430615##q1_a1##3WYZV0QBFLRUS7BT4K9I30FFCGIBX0", "type": "mcq", "stem": "So yesterday I called up their support center to try to get the problem fixed . Microsoft was willing to work on the case despite the fact that I bought the console used from GameStop . After futzing around for a while with cables and trying to get it working , they suggested that I get a new A / V cable . So I went out and bought myself a new A / V cable .\n\nQuestion: What may i be trying to get fixed ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "My playstation", "C": "My laptop", "D": "My x box"}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 6515, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3E24UO25QZOMYXHZN4TEH9EMT5V6OA##36AHBNMV1SA0Z4YATHGSEQI41ESDYL##A3H0TLQC53H5MB##Blog_847948##q2_a1##3PN6H8C9R64BBR1K768AEISHEJKDAA", "type": "mcq", "stem": "No flying brooms . Bugger ! But the bludgers were contorted teddy - bears , and the snitch was a Nemo squeaky rubber toy , and for all that I thought I 'd only gone to be a spectator , I ended up as one of the volunteers who threw the snitch * and * thoroughly enjoyed myself , despite having problems seeing the snitch on occasions . The number of players increased , play hotted up and became fiercely competitive , but also wildly fun .\n\nQuestion: What fictional character might the OP be ?", "options": {"A": "Harry Potter", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "Beatrice Prior", "D": "Evan Walker"}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 23462, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3R5LWXWHR06BPZKX08PWCDI4ZWBGXH##33M4IA01QHZ509R56MPA01SZGLCXRI##AS5X6GRDJKWG3##Blog_277735##q1_a1##3WRAAIUSBLDP9X61Y69M8PV9U7YAXN", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Today I asked Josh if we had a socket wrench . He showed me how to actually use one , and together we detached the whole fan mechanism , reattached the screw , put the whole thing back together , and voila ! The fan works like new . Our apartment is cooler , and the peasants rejoiced .\n\nQuestion: What may be a fact about the person speaking ?", "options": {"A": "They had to purchase a new fan .", "B": "They had to get a new fan for their apartment .", "C": "They had fixed their broken fan .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 21295, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3UOMW19E6FK40TJPCEMIM1UD0S6C5B##3B2X28YI3ZUKWCPRTZ6US7YK34FB6Z##AS5X6GRDJKWG3##Blog_727903##q2_a1##33QQ60S6AUW1RGEO1Z16ZCKSR0GU0T", "type": "mcq", "stem": "It was basically the same every day . Wake up , put on clothes , eat breakfast , weed and then shower . In the middle of the day I would do desk work or we would lay around reading .\n\nQuestion: What may be the reason for their routine ?", "options": {"A": "They want to minimize socializing .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "They are used to it .", "D": "They want to stay inside ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 22981, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3IVEC1GSLRDSKPOCLJ1S6FUREHB1J3##39DD6S19JSQKRPLM5V5VQDX0COSEZZ##AS5X6GRDJKWG3##Blog_645909##q2_a1##3IKDQS3DQGEGCHE4JY5CBAYI6X6CII", "type": "mcq", "stem": "It 's a long way to be sustainable country in China . but these nice persons action will change China for sustainable country all over the world . I will walk through China and all over the world not only for China for our earth .\n\nQuestion: How might this person be described ?", "options": {"A": "They are an active person .", "B": "They are an athletic person .", "C": "They are an activist for the environment .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 17856, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3NSM4HLQNT8XNGC61OBG4HEL1OPQQ9##3C44YUNSI44LLF5GMRW9TXD159LDPG##A35BKXOE6C5ITG##Blog_1248339##q2_a1##32K26U12DP2V3F4II1Z6A56UZ53DVH", "type": "mcq", "stem": "We knew there was a tyre shop in Killarney so we rode the spare till we got there . On the way we stopped at my favorite place of the whole trip . It was \" Molly 's Tea Room . \"\n\nQuestion: what is molly 's tea room most likely ?", "options": {"A": "a place to order tea", "B": "a place that gives films about tea", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "a place that does not sell tea"}, "answer": ["A"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 13746, "label_index": 0}}
{"id": "3538U0YQ1FSTV1HO5ZCQNCTORMA3F5##3EF8EXOTT2TGCKNZROVU31271ORJ16##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_339042##q1_a1##3XABXM4AJ3JRHCCAFUUGIQTL7GAQ81", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I have a friend who maintains that I have extra - ordinary curiosity and she dislikes the way I stop and gaze at something that has caught my fancy . I must admit sometimes I get carried away especially with planes and I once landed into a ditch because an aircraft that was passing quite low near my university in London , looked good to my eyes ! I like jets and I ' m already dreaming of travelling in the colossal Airbus A380 ! !\n\nQuestion: Why is the friend getting annoyed with the narrator ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "The narrator keeps staring at things .", "C": "The narrator is difficult to work with at university .", "D": "The narrator is dropping out of university ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 7223, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "33K3E8REWWTWWKEFHAD8K016AI88XC##3LO69W1SU4BJBP12CSSAQ3J52STLGZ##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_939412##q1_a1##3D5G8J4N5A2NQF18KTNLNB089N1VT8", "type": "mcq", "stem": "So this morning I thought I was being proactive and getting dinner in the crock pot to cook all day . The idea of smelling a brisket with potatoes and carrots and onions cooking all say sounded heavenly . I got everything all chopped up and into the crock pot . I threw in some chopped up garlic and put the lid on .\n\nQuestion: What is the narrator desiring next once her prep is done ?", "options": {"A": "The narrator will want to go on a fast .", "B": "The narrator will want to make food .", "C": "The narrator will want to eat .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 14719, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "3NSCTNUR211G7EMRS0QRG64PZA8A5Z##3K3R2QNK8EIMAU0VRXQ1H7HAGASU9A##A1VYRD3HO2WDUN##Blog_677613##q1_a1##3TUOHPJXYJBMGA94ZB5EQES0MJKXWQ", "type": "mcq", "stem": "So we hugged and I left Dan to the care of the airline - this time , however , not stuck in a wheelchair , and not shivering with a fever . So , much better than last time!I rode the trains back to Wada , uneventfully , except to say that I had to stand for an hour and a half or so , at the start of it all , as there were no seats left in the trains . I got back to Wada at 7 pm , and I took a taxi ( GASP , YES ) from Wada station to the old people 's home near my house . Why ?\n\nQuestion: What may be a valid fact about the train ?", "options": {"A": "Dan and I rode on it .", "B": "It was packed with riders .", "C": "It stopped right by my house .", "D": "None of the above choices ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 19309, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "3FI30CQHVMXH9SRX3X0S3N2VFGJ6B9##3MYYFCXHJ6M286TOQX5TWK53QC74G5##A3PPLDHC3CG0YN##Blog_823731##q1_a1##3Y7LTZE0YV0YT1KE5TEY5BNE9EEUZE", "type": "mcq", "stem": "We rigged it up so that it works again , but it 's no longer a textbook SPL system . We 're going to keep up the meds for another week , but reduce her Banamine from 500 # twice a day to 500 # once a day . Rosie did not act like a lady for Megan today .\n\nQuestion: What may be the reason why they needed to adjust the medicine ?", "options": {"A": "They could n't afford it anymore .", "B": "They wanted to see if she did n't need it anymore .", "C": "They want to try a natural approach .", "D": "It was no longer working ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 9115, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3TL87MO8CMNAB57DB5GQJYN5R1ELF0##3ITXP059PXHG64MT47AEZ2PGPM9JSP##A2KYOM2ZGYDJGT##Blog_1032625##q1_a1##3DZKABX2ZKJLYNY4I54VQZOCEUACVD", "type": "mcq", "stem": "We did our first track and were stopped by the manager - turn down or get off . It almost came to blows when , standing in the tin shed and unable to hear above the amp hum , he thought we were giving him lip . We turned down and trundled through the first few songs with decided lacklustre . After a bit of tweaking we got to a decent level and kicked out the last three tracks with vim and vigour ( and some good ol' head banging).Mark from Psych Carni had gone all out with lights , smoke , P.A.\n\nQuestion: What 's the possible reason they were stopped by the manager ?", "options": {"A": "They were standing in a tin shed .", "B": "The music was too loud .", "C": "They finished the first track .", "D": "They wanted to come to blows ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 212, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "30OITAWPBSHEIOWH1WD098WV0SIH9T##3MYYFCXHJ6M286TOQX5TWK53QYNG45##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_1261836##q1_a2##3UOMW19E6FK40TJPCEMIM1UD1EP5CW", "type": "mcq", "stem": "As I mentioned before , we were fortunate enough to be in Reykjavik when the silver medal handball team came home . It was really nice to be part of the festivities and celebration . It felt as though a large majority of the Icelandic people were there , considering so many people showed up . While we were walking through town we saw their plane fly into the city airport escorted by two helicopters and we knew it would be a large event .\n\nQuestion: Why was so many people at the airport ?", "options": {"A": "To cheer the visiting Icelandic team .", "B": "To cheer the home team .", "C": "None of the above choices .", "D": "To cheer the visiting team from Reykjavic ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 24864, "label_index": 1}}
{"id": "36MUZ9VAE8GE14IWNBAWA1I8ZX5EDR##3WR9XG3T66QJFDINXU1ZQ7SARTJ744##A3PPLDHC3CG0YN##Blog_802230##q1_a1##3M47JKRKCZFY7UTQ0LGICLCU7IE686", "type": "mcq", "stem": "Of course , 1812 completely ignored Mija , and I was able to distract her from her fearsome guarding behavior with a chance to play tug - of - war with the pheasant stuffie . Tired of the stuffie , we then moved on to my favorite toy . Early in the evening , I carried the pheasant stuffie outside to see if I could get anyone to play with me . Peaches looked like she might want to play , but Mija was a bit unsure about getting in a game that involved the alpha dog .\n\nQuestion: What kind of pets does the speaker have ?", "options": {"A": "Cats .", "B": "None of the above choices .", "C": "Birds .", "D": "Dogs ."}, "answer": ["D"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 5231, "label_index": 3}}
{"id": "3NQUW096N8MG4KF7SHSY10P2HL29LR##30LB5CDZNFPL0Z6SXO6G5OVWM1VZ07##A1GV0UZU0T2ORS##Blog_1169926##q2_a1##351S7I5UGBAVYWV1Q6ZQ3M7VJ0RNJC", "type": "mcq", "stem": "No ! Just because I do n't go around saying how hot my boss is , and I instead take to insulting her when I damn well please , does n't mean I ' m obsessed with her ! \" \" Uhm ... I think you are , \" Antoine said tentatively . I glared at him .\n\nQuestion: Why did I shoot Antoine the look that I did ?", "options": {"A": "It 's made me sarcastic .", "B": "It 's made me happy .", "C": "It 's made me angry .", "D": "It makes me want to laugh ."}, "answer": ["C"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 22876, "label_index": 2}}
{"id": "324N5FAHSZP3HLASAILTEI1KJ3IKVX##3TMFV4NEPBTZOT6QH5ZOZZ7WMHSW8S##A3VVR8NR3ED04C##Blog_1144472##q1_a1##3TZ0XG8CBWYLPDVOYSJUWV3WXKX98X", "type": "mcq", "stem": "I met with my advisor / prof yesterday about my upcoming paper . In the process of emails and the meeting , he offered me a super sweet deal on a faculty apartment near the school . I took it and had to drag my stuff there this morning .\n\nQuestion: What type of school is the narrator in ?", "options": {"A": "None of the above choices .", "B": "They are at university .", "C": "They are at a prep school .", "D": "They are at an advisory school ."}, "answer": ["B"], "answer_format": "letters", "source": {"csv_path": "data/train.csv", "row_index": 13848, "label_index": 1}}
